A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education and Public Policy Program (EPP), Education and Research Division (E&R), Program Files FA633
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Mario Fantino Files, 1952-1970; XIV
  - Mario Fantini Subject Files, 1952-1970; XIV.2
    - Outgoing Letters, 1965 (Box 27)
    - Educational Services Incorporated (ESI), 1965 (Box 27)
    - Model School Systems of Future, 1965-1967 (Box 27)
    - Trip -- Model Systems, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Fantini European Trip, 1966 (Box 27)
- James Armsey Subject Files, 1957-1967; XV
  - Bowles, Frank, 1966 (Box 28)
  - Faust, Clarence, 1964-1965 (Box 28)
  - Dressner, Howard, 1966-1967 (Box 28)
  - Hardy, Gladys, 1965 (Box 28)
  - Schmid, Robert, 1966 (Box 28)
  - Undergraduate Education -- University College -- Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 28)
  - Domestic Program Directors Meeting, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
  - Policy and Planning Memoranda, 1965 (Box 28)
  - Urban Universities, 1965 (Box 28)
  - Administrative Review Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 28)
  - Stone Committee -- Citizen Education in World Affairs, 1965 (Box 28)
  - McCloy Committee, 1962 (Box 28)
  - Kenya ETV -- Iran ETV, 1962 (Box 28)
  - India ETV Report, 1960 (Box 28)
  - Colombia ETV Report, 1963 (Box 28)
  - United Arab Republic (UAR) ETV Report, 1962 (Box 28)
  - Manilla ETV Report, 1962-1966 (Box 28)
  - Brazil ETV Report, 1964 (Box 28)
  - NETC, 1966 (Box 28)
  - Carnegie Commission on ETV, 1965 (Box 28)
  - NET -- WNDT -- ETV, 1966 (Box 28)
  - International ETV, 1961-1966 (Box 28)
  - ETV -- General, 1959-1966 (Box 28)
  - ETV -- Long Range Planning, 1962-1963 (Box 28)
- College Grants Program, 1953-1956; XVI
  - College Grants Program -- Accomplishment Grants -- 2nd Payments, 1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Correspondence with FF Trustees re: Formation of Committee and Committee Actions, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- FF Internal Memoranda and Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Accomplishment Grants -- 1st Payments, n.d. (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Endowment Grants -- 2nd Payment (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program Chronology -- Ford Foundation Actions, 1955-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program Chronology -- Questionnaires, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Endowment Grants -- 1st Payment, 1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Form Letters to Advisory Committee, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Allen, Raymond B., 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Allen, William M., 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Black, James B., 1955-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Butterfield, Victor L., 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Bryan, Malcolm, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Corson, John J., 1956-1957 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Gannon, Rev. Robert I., 1955-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Josephs, Devereux C., 1955-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Lee, Mrs. John G., 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Lovett, Robert A., 1955-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Millett, John D., 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Morrill, James L., 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Stern, Edgar B., 1955-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee -- Wilson, Logan, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee Meeting, Jun 27, 1953 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee Meeting, Oct 18, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee Meeting, Dec 6, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Advisory Committee Report to Ford Foundation, Dec 8, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program -- Corson-Fels-Josephs Correspondence, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program Staff -- Campbell, Herman C., 1955-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program Staff -- Fels, William C., 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program Consultant -- Sheldon, Richard C., 1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program Consultants -- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1955 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program Chronology -- Committee Staff Memoranda and Tabulations, 1955-1956 (Box 29)
  - College Grants Program Chronology -- Advisory Committee Correspondence and Action, 1955 (Box 29)
- Special Projects in Education (SPE) -- Reuben Frodin Subject Files, 1955-1968; XVII
  - Endowment and Enrollment Charts -- Meeting, Sep 29, 1967 (Box 30)
  - Special Programs Background Information, 1960 (Box 30)
  - Data on College Grants Program, 1955-1956 (Box 30)
  - Letter and Questionnaire, Feb 1, 1968 (Box 30)
  - College Grants Program -- Information, 1955-1956 (Box 30)
  - Miss Eunice Cooper -- Correspondence, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Memorandum re: College Grants Program, Jun 19, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Review of SPE -- Original Typescript, [1968] (Box 30)
  - Hans Jenny Study Data, [1968] (Box 30)
  - Tables I, II, III -- Enrollment, Cost per Student, Tuition, [1968] (Box 30)
  - Table VI, Item 1 -- 1967 vs 1956 Endowment, [1968] (Box 30)
  - Table VI, Item 2 -- Payroll, Tuition, Enrollment, Endowment, [1968] (Box 30)
  - Table VI, Item 5 -- 1967 vs. 1956 Tuition, [1968] (Box 30)
  - Table VI, Item 7 -- 1967 vs 1956 Salaries, [1968] (Box 30)
  - Table VI, Item 8 -- 1967 Salaries vs Ford Grant, [1968] (Box 30)
  - Section IV -- Special Program Review, 1967 (Box 30)
  - Statistical Analyses -- Information Management, Inc., 1967 (Box 30)
  - I M I Correspondence (H. Roseman), 1968 (Box 30)
  - Colleges That Failed to Return Questionnaire, 1968 (Box 30)
  - F. Champion Ward -- Information Paper to Board Recommending Termination of Special Project in Education, Dec 1968 (Box 30)
  - Frodin Report to Ward and Ward Report to Bundy, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Special Program Review -- Internal Document, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Dimensions -- Original Typescript, n.d. (Box 30)
  - Special Projects in Education -- Grant Data Sorted Alphabetically by Grantee, Numerically by Program Action Number, 1967 (Box 30)
  - SPE Lists -- Colleges and University Financial Memoranda and Statements, 1960-1963 (Box 30)
  - Special Project in Education (SPE), 1960-1966 (Box 30)
  - SPE -- Frodin Paper and Termination Paper, 1967 (Box 30)
- Edward J. Meade Files, XVIII
  - Edward J. Meade Correspondence Files, 1963-1973; XVIII.1
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr-Jun 1963 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1963 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1963 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1964 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr-Jun 1964 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1964 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1964 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1965 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr-Jun 1965 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1965 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1965 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1965 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1965 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1965 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1965 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, May 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1966 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1967 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1967 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1967 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1967 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, May 1967 (Box 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1967 (Box 31)
    - Memoranda, 1967 (Box 32)
    - Memoranda, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1967 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1967 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1967 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1967 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1967 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1967 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, May 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1968 (Box 32)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1968 (Box 32)
    - Vocational Education, n.d. (Box 32)
    - Chile, 1963-1964 (Box 32)
    - Survey of Vocational and Technical Education Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 32)
    - Commission on the Humanities in the Schools, 1968-1969 (Box 33)
    - Memoranda, 1969 (Box 33)
    - Memoranda, 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, May 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1969 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, May 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1970 (Box 33)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1970 (Box 33)
    - Alphabetical Correspondence -- A-C, 1968 (Box 34)
    - Alphabetical Correspondence -- D-G, 1968 (Box 34)
    - Alphabetical Correspondence -- H-I, 1968 (Box 34)
    - Alphabetical Correspondence -- K-P, 1968 (Box 34)
    - Alphabetical Correspondence -- B-C, 1970 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, May 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1971 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, May 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1972 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jan 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Feb 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Mar 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Apr 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, May 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Oct 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Nov 1973 (Box 34)
    - Chronological Correspondence, Dec 1973 (Box 34)
  - Edward J. Meade Subject Files, 1960-1972; XVIII.2
    - American Association of Junior Colleges -- General, 1965 (Box 35)
    - American Management Association -- Conference, Aug 9-12, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Bank Street College of Education, 1966 (Box 35)
    - A-B, 1965-1966 (Box 35)
    - C-D, 1965-1966 (Box 35)
    - Center for Applied Linguistics -- General, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Center for Urban Education -- General, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Coordinating Council on Education for the Disadvantaged, 1965-1966 (Box 35)
    - Comprehensive School Improvement -- General, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Comprehensive School Improvement -- Bohrson Reports, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Comprehensive School Improvement -- Conference, Jan 1966 (Box 35)
    - Committee on Assessing the Progress of Education, 1965-1967 (Box 35)
    - Defense Advisory Committee on Education, 1964 (Box 35)
    - Delegation of Authority, 1964 (Box 35)
    - New Jersey Senate Education Bill S-434, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Governor's Conference on Education (NJ), Apr 2, 1966 (Box 35)
    - E-F, 1965-1966 (Box 35)
    - G, 1965-1966 (Box 35)
    - H, 1965-1966 (Box 35)
    - Harvard University -- General Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 35)
    - A-D General, 1967 (Box 36)
    - E-I General, 1967 (Box 36)
    - K-M General, 1967 (Box 36)
    - N-S General, 1967 (Box 36)
    - T-Z General, 1967 (Box 36)
    - Alaska -- General, 1966-1967 (Box 36)
    - Atlantic Colleges (The), 1967 (Box 36)
    - CSI -- Center for the Study of Instruction (of the NEA), 1966 (Box 36)
    - Committee on Assessing the Progress of Education, 1967 (Box 36)
    - Civil Liberties and Constitutional Rights -- General, 1967 (Box 36)
    - Education Commission of the States -- Working File, 1968 (Box 36)
    - Elementary School Teaching Project -- General, 1965 (Box 36)
    - Fund for the Advancement of Education -- General, 1968 (Box 36)
    - Fund for the Advancement of Education -- Personnel, 1965-1966 (Box 36)
    - Instructional Television (ITV) -- General, 1967-1968 (Box 36)
    - ITV Weekend -- Working File, 1967 (Box 36)
    - Memoranda -- General, 1960 (Box 37)
    - Memoranda -- General, 1961 (Box 37)
    - Memoranda -- General, 1962 (Box 37)
    - Memoranda -- General, 1963 (Box 37)
    - Memoranda -- General, 1964 (Box 37)
    - Memoranda -- General, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Memoranda -- General, 1966 (Box 37)
    - Overseas Dependents Schools -- General, 1961-1962 (Box 37)
    - Overseas Dependents Schools -- General, 1963 (Box 37)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1962 (Box 37)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1963 (Box 37)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1964 (Box 37)
    - Program Development -- Miscellaneous Background Materials, 1960 (Box 37)
    - Comprehensive School Improvement -- General, 1960-1961 (Box 37)
    - American Management Association -- Educational Technology Conference, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Language and Linguistics -- General, 1967 (Box 37)
    - Manpower Planning and Development -- General, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Mayor's Advisory Panel on Decentralization of the New York City Schools, 1967-1968 (Box 37)
    - PBL -- Public Broadcast Laboratory, 1967 (Box 37)
    - Georgia-Kansas -- Correspondence Accompanying Data, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Kentucky-New Jersey -- Correspondence Accompanying Data, 1968 (Box 38)
    - New York-North Carolina -- Correspondence Accompanying Data, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Ohio-Tennessee -- Correspondence Accompanying Data, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Texas-Wisconsin -- Correspondence Accompanying Data, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Memorandum re: Integration, Mar 20, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Language and Linguistics -- Miscellaneous Reports and Memoranda, 1968-1970 (Box 38)
    - Newark, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Pre-School Programs, 1964 (Box 38)
    - Reading Specialists, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Teacher Training, 1962-1966 (Box 38)
    - Television, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Temple University, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Two Year Colleges, 1965 (Box 38)
    - Meade Speech -- The College: Where Do We Go from Here?, Jun 4, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Correspondence -- Miscellaneous (1/2), 1968-1972 (Box 38)
    - Correspondence -- Miscellaneous (2/2), 1968-1972 (Box 38)
    - BNS Satellite Files - Eastern Educational Network (EEN), 1967 (Box 39)
    - BNS Satellite Files - FCC Proposal -- Claire List, 1967 (Box 39)
    - BNS Satellite Files - Satellite, 1966 (Box 39)
    - BNS Satellite Files - ITV File I -- Responses to FEC's 9/26 Letter, 1966 (Box 39)
    - BNS Satellite Files - Replies to Receipt of Submission from Mr. Bundy, Aug 1966 (Box 39)
    - BNS Satellite Files - Background (Notes, Memoranda) for BNS, 1966 (Box 39)
    - BNS Satellite Files - Satellite Materials (1/3), 1966 (Box 39)
    - BNS Satellite Files - Satellite Materials (2/3), 1966 (Box 39)
    - BNS Satellite Files - Satellite Materials (3/3), 1966 (Box 39)
    - School Improvement Program -- Fact Sheets, 1965-1966 (Box 40)
    - Comprehensive School Improvement Program, 1965-1966 (Box 40)
    - Social Studies Projects, 1965-1966 (Box 40)
    - School Health, 1966 (Box 40)
    - Center for Occupational Education, 1968 (Box 40)
    - Accreditation, 1968 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence -- General, 1968-1969 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence -- Alumni Association, 1968 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence -- Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence -- Chancellor, 1968-1969 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence -- Liggitt, 1967-1968 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence -- Mullen (President), 1968-1969 (Box 40)
    - Faculty Associations -- General, 1967-1968 (Box 40)
    - Meetings -- Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 40)
    - Selection of President -- Candidates, 1968 (Box 40)
    - Selection of President -- General, 1968 (Box 40)
    - Reports of Education Team -- Vietnam, Mar 1966 (Box 41)
    - HEW Vietnam Health-Education Task Force Briefing Book, 1962-1966 (Box 41)
    - N, 1965-1966 (Box 41)
    - National Council of Teachers of English, 1965 (Box 41)
    - National Education Association (NEA), 1966 (Box 41)
    - National Institute of Mental Health -- General, 1965 (Box 41)
    - Negro Teachers -- General, 1965 (Box 41)
    - North Carolina Fund -- General, 1965 (Box 41)
    - New York City -- Board of Education, 1965-1966 (Box 41)
    - O, 1965-1966 (Box 41)
    - Overseas Dependents Schools, 1966 (Box 41)
    - P, 1965-1966 (Box 41)
    - Q, 1965 (Box 41)
    - R, 1966 (Box 41)
    - S, 1965-1967 (Box 41)
    - T, 1966 (Box 41)
    - U, 1965-1966 (Box 41)
    - United Nations International School -- General, 1965 (Box 41)
    - United States Office of Education -- Title IV, 1965-1966 (Box 41)
    - Vocational Education in Vietnam, 1966 (Box 41)
    - W, 1965-1966 (Box 41)
    - War on Poverty -- President's Task Force, 1965 (Box 41)
    - X-Z, 1966-1967 (Box 41)
    - I, 1966 (Box 42)
    - International Schools Services (ISS) -- General, 1965 (Box 42)
    - I.T.A. -- Bethlehem, 1965-1966 (Box 42)
    - J, 1965-1966 (Box 42)
    - Journal of Human Resources -- University of Wisconsin, 1965-1966 (Box 42)
    - K, 1965-1967 (Box 42)
    - Kamehameha Schools -- General, 1965 (Box 42)
    - L, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Latin America -- Argentina/Chile, 1963-1964 (Box 42)
    - Latin America -- Argentina/Chile, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Latin America -- Brazil, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Latin America -- General, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Latin America -- Manpower, 1966 (Box 42)
    - London, University of -- Reading Research Unit, 1966 (Box 42)
    - M, 1965-1966 (Box 42)
    - Mc, 1965-1966 (Box 42)
    - Memoranda -- M. Feldman, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Memoranda -- M. Fantini, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Memoranda -- General, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Memoranda -- F. Bowles, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Minority Groups -- General, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Montclair State College -- Alumni Association Stationery, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Montclair State College -- Margin for Excellence Project, 1965 (Box 42)
- Public Education Chronological Correspondence Files, Jun-Sep 1969; XIX
  - Public Education Chronological Correspondence, Jun 1-15, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Public Education Chronological Correspondence, Jun 16-30, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Public Education Chronological Correspondence, Jul 1-15, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Public Education Chronological Correspondence, Jul 16-31, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Public Education Chronological Correspondence, Aug 1-15, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Public Education Chronological Correspondence, Aug 16-31, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Public Education Chronological Correspondence, Sep 1-15, 1969 (Box 42)
  - Public Education Chronological Correspondence, Sep 16-30, 1969 (Box 42)
- Cox/Chafkin Miscellaneous Office Files, 1958-1979; XX
  - Instructional Television Production Techniques, Jun 25-27, 1962 (Box 43)
  - National Program, Sep 1963 (Box 43)
  - National Program in the Use of Television in the Public Schools -- Report on the First Year 1957-1958, Jan 1959 (Box 43)
  - National Program in the Use of Television in the Public Schools -- Some Reflections on the First Year, Jun 10, 1958 (Box 43)
  - National Program in the Use of Television in the Public Schools -- Report on the Second Year, Jun 1960 (Box 43)
  - National Program in the Use of Television in the Public Schools -- Report on the Third Year, May 1961 (Box 43)
  - Two-Year College Survey, 1965 (Box 43)
  - National Affairs Current Programs -- Background and Review, Nov 1, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Conference on the Electoral Process, Jan 27, 1969 (Box 43)
  - FY 1978 Management Budget, 1977 (Box 43)
  - National Affairs -- Budget Planning -- Memoranda and Papers, 1974-1977 (Box 43)
  - Select Committee Memoranda re: Bundy Report, 1968 (Box 43)
  - Report of the Select Committee on the Future of Private and Independent Higher Education in New York State, Jan 1968 (Box 43)
  - Select Committee on the Future of Private and Independent Higher Education in New York State -- Introductory Letters to Mr. Bundy from Governor Rockefeller, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Study of the Financial Needs of Selected Private and Independent Higher Educational Institutions in New York State, Oct 1967 (Box 43)
  - Select Committee on the Future of Private and Independent Higher Education in New York State -- Observations and Notes, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Mr. Bundy, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Albany -- Administrative, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Cartter Papers, 1967 (Box 43)
  - June 23-24 Meetings, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Heald Report, 1960 (Box 43)
  - New York University -- An Analysis for the Select Committee, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Preliminary Agenda, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Address by W. Allen Wallis, 1964 (Box 43)
  - Wells' Committee, 1964 (Box 43)
  - Background Documents, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Nelson Associates, 1967 (Box 43)
  - American Council on Education -- National File, 1967 (Box 43)
- Sol Chafkin Subject Files, 1972-1981; XXI